[music]
[музыка]
Angry view delivery plus sign, how else
энгри вид поставка плюсик чем иначе ты
can you see normally
видно нормально
delivery plus sign so that she spends the night
поставка плюсик чтобы она ночует и
and bachata and looks like normal rooks and I
бачаты и и выгляд нормальный грачи а я
decide the stream preview there
там видом решается превьюшка стрима
because these batchchat and you picture there
потому что эти батчат и вы картинку там
until the Russian soldier ticks for  that the
до российский солдат тикать ибо что
beads and the fund of some kind
бисера и фонд некий
show me a gray background, I put the
мне показываю серый фон я поставил
picture, but it would not look like it draws a
картинку но не бы на вид обращает
preview of the streams
превьюшку стримах
to drag them, i.e.  batey
тащить их т.е. батей
cool yes here and put on other times the
прикольно да вот и надевают другие раз
same extreme it turns out that the
таки extreme выходит что
preview of the x stream is just stupidly siro
превью х стрима просто тупо сиро
ucoz hand filmed yes today being from the
ucoz рукой снимало да сегодня будучи от
helm .  today we will be in the village of blue test
руля . сегодня будем в селе теста синего
we have
нас have
flowers yefim on such same
цветков ефим на такие вот же
scoreboard picture
табло картинка
in ten kubachi yes
в тэн кубачи да
yes someone to fill the picture doctor fish I’m
да хто бачить картинку доктор рыбачить я
tedious 27 matches for
нудных 27 матчей на
yes and we start our today’s
да и начинаем наш сегодняшний
our today’s number so with the help of
нашу сегодняшнюю могут числ так помощью
we lectures mathematics queen of science every
мы лекций математика царица науки каждый
yes and  at home we will rise to whose magic
да и дома подымемся на чьи магические
numbers c skilka shop arches dzhen bought a
числа c скильки цех арки джен купили
call for in ukraine for a fee according to the data of the
зова на в украине платно за данным
general staff for yesterday and the day before yesterday it was at
генштаба за вчера и позавчера была на
300 + 350 good-natured people so looked and
300 + 350 добряки так посмотрел и
cutlets and e in total 53 thousand three hundred
котлеты и е суммарно 53 тысячи триста
so you are still surprised,
так-то вы удивляет еще
let's say for happy
скажем за рады
wings  whom the body of a dwarf is so prestor
крыльев кого тела карлика так престор
someone bush vilno russia has already lost to
кого-то буш вильно россия утратила уже
soldiers and fruits that such a
солдатам и фрукты что такие
regional center of the century from the place of power and everything is
райцентра веке с места силы так и все
so the visualizer is somehow an alley outside the
так визуализатор как-то аллея вне
people of him, but not at the expense of mucho for the
людей ним а ведь не за счет mucho для
empire for the empire people c just
империи для империи людына c просто
material and  who can put and tan a
материал и ком можно ставить и загар
mat
мату
would you at rallies
бы ты на митингах
paper we face and and while here for
бумагу мы по лицам и и тогда как тут для
the Qing empire the meat of the river is just you
империи цин мясо реке просто вы
cross to capture new territories
крестовую для захвата новых территорий
in this misfortune  tnoy masha bang lava growth
в этом несчастной машу грохну лава росту
masha dad
маша папаша
i.e.  tatyana moderator
т.е. татьяна модератор
further such syans will be like this I will appear on these
дальше такие сьяны будут такими я на эти
machines on the site and then who
машины быть появлялись на сайт да то кто
else understands the
разумеет еще
saints klein this returns to the defense
святые клейн это возвращает на оборонный
budget scarlet well let's say now you
бюджет алая ну скажем в ныне вы дуете
blow stacks of mine there they came and a slipper and
стаки там моих же пришли то и тапку а
damn coins epic wedge from military
блин монетки эпическом клин от военно
under  widow I will attack on and so on the right in
под вдова я нападу на на и так справа в
that still nature is not yet the history of people in the
том еще природе не еще история люд во
past
прошла
history the feeling has passed at the wine the whole
история чувство прошло у вина вся
history of the chandelier of the virgin lands so there is a tribe
история люстра целины так там есть племя
stan was sleeping them 10 masses people and
стэн было спать им 10 масс народ и
pedal lvts passages sv from the primary
педаль лвц проходы св из первичный розно
rozno there well authoritatively
там ну властно
do  for a long time, well, he eats both cheese and meat
cдeлaть давно ну там ест и сыр и мясо
there was the norm, everything or cheese and meat weren’t there
было норма все или сыр и мясо не было
three personal plugs so overgrown sho you
три личными пробки так зарастает шо вы
days will catch and the blue will be her and Christs
days поймает и голубое будет ее и христы
appear on you yak puffed up the truth with a plus sign
на вас появляется як надымила правда
so that the mekhmat are taken
посадкой плюсик чтобы мехмата взяты
just normally not from hunger atheists
просто нормально не с голоду атеисты
head  you’ll pierce the gunner’s cheese and
голову сырок комендор проткнете дотка и
go dumb and not
стрёмный зайти и бы не
having obviously got a rental, well, in particular, they would
добрав явно прокат ну в частности их бы
n’t be in Maine, and there, in short, I can
не было в мэн и там короче я может
look in and I wouldn’t see him like that, although
заглянуть и виду я бы не его так хотя
our ancestors  que es great-great-great-great-grandfather’s great-great-grandfather,
наши предки que es прапрапрапра прадеда
so this cru was this chun and lived
так вот вот это кру был этому чун и жила
in stone you will see on the main sheet
в каменном увидите на главных шитова
bottom of the window and
днище окна и
so 8kl from the bull and let’s say makis there a slave
так 8кл из булл и скажем макис там раба
dominance needle sensor feudal if
властность игла датчик феодальный если
this at a time we will give out thoughts you are used to from
это за раз мы выдам мысли ты привык от
Igor it will be deku  so a very
игорем это будет дэку тобто весьма
ancient ram
стародавний рэм
there bulo slaves well, like that at a time they
там було рабы ну а like что за раз
fed it be say I want to have two
питали it be скажи я хочу завести два
slaves so and equis there
раба так и equis там
paid land on blacks a recipe for a [ __ ]
платных земли на черных рецепт на дебила
and kira would be so your type and a construction
и кира бы так твой типаж и строительном
yard and a
дворик и костюму
kolyma costume for him and but capes  dodiki i vova
колымы ним и а вот накидки додики я вова
putin v doesn’t want her mastic still
путин в не хочет мастики свои таки
see que es tan mi new tulip inn st
увидим que es tan mi новых tulip inn st
participants she peeks out smoke from the price of the
участниц она выглядывает дым от цены
size of men
разме мужчин
bool1 and
bool1 и
bool2 quite rented i will often
bool2 весьма напрокат я от будет часто
attach cyprus and ktk uk
приложит кипр и ктк великобритания
who knows the amount to force them that is
кто знает сумму заставлять их то есть
back i  read 2 rocky then mazda this is the
назад я читал 2 роки то mazda это
UK on music or cinematavre
великобритания на музыке или кинотавре
artists all sorts of music there is not 13 whales of
артисты всякие там музыку их не 13 кита
billions of dollars someone around the
миллиардов долларов кто то по всему
world magic cults so there are
свету магические культы так там студии
recording studios opti  small I understand so
звукозаписи оптимальный разбираюсь так
heptyl of the industry and gluing Britain
гептила индустрии и у склейки британия
with caustic
едким
fur to the saints collected adds a bunch of
меховом до святым собрано добавляет кучу
good note so they don’t and the massacre of the studio
хорошей ноте так их не и резни студии
sleep wiki and then in particular
спи вики и тогда тому в частности
to fight and what Izard Andy buys there
воевать и что там закупает изард энди
so that our dances get out of the way past the essence
чтоб танцев наши убираться мимо essence
so you can for  a ruble from their grove on a
так-то ты можешь за рубль от их роще на
steeply twisted 650 to her brush there 200
набагато крути 650 до ей кисть там 200
floated up with a view that is no longer the grass of the
всплывали с вид меняется то уже не трава
parish you would be there, your
прихода ты и бы то там пуховики ваши
children’s down jackets would rise up on belts there 2
дети упоротее повышалась на ремни там 2
.  17 18 to this candida background well, for the split
. 17 18 к этому candida фон ну за раскол
and we share tangible if there are mid empires
и мы делимся ощутим если там империи мид
and they had a territory of insoles in
и у них были а территории стельки в
Russia, we can’t live there and
россии мы там не может и
from now on you can blow it just like
обжить отныне можете дул она просто так
that, your ipsc metro is not your ipsc arsenic damask mother and
не метро ваша ipsc мышьяк булатом мать и
there they need a cow  bulo chemistry
там корове им треба було химичить
would be slammed shut and what do you come in you
захлопнуты бы и что ты на заходишь ты
demons and treba bulo people pasture nike
бесов и треба було людям пастей nike
here 2 .  we will go around attacking the bone and
здесь 2 . мы обойдем на кость нападат и
above the Maidan is shorter so that we are attacked
above короче майдан чтобы на нас напал
it is less he and was at a time of
это меньше он и был за раз
realization people have a sea from lu
реализации у людей море от лу
guests soared not such muslin as
гости парились не такие кисеи как у
Putin’s cotton wool is bought there
путина вате бажання закупается там
grabs and respects and respects Elon Musk to
захапает и и уважал и уважает илон маск
wear and soaked q  Screenshot and Elon Musk to
носить и вымоченный q скрину и илон маск
intercede for additional guilt, I’m not in the
заступить за допомогою вины я не при
year of Alaska tilda Elon Musk Elon Musk
году аляски тильда илон маск илон маск
after that, but in a quiet denunciation, this is Putin
после то так а в тихий донос это путин
Putin and you beat the Euro-6 economy at the price of
путин и тебе бил экономики евро-6 цене
this,
этому
we want intelligence and a little not darkness to achieve
хотим ума и малости не темноте добиться
stream
стрим
that in
тому
particular in particular  hat primates
частности в су частности шапка приматы
on the shaft lithuania so that the primates of the year on his
по валу литву чтобы приматы году на его
signboard run out of the cudgel and you would be crazy by the
вывеска выбегать из дубину и бы ты псих
sexes measured and who doesn’t change those
полами измеряется а кто нет меняется тех
dinosaurs go he and be
динозавры идут он и будь
it don’t forget let’s at a time we will
так не забудь давайте за раз мы будем
give videos so don’t forget them too
давайтесь ролики так не забудь их тоже
for 15 subscribers per kilogram  channel
на 15 подписчица на килограмм канальчик
me
me
now I'm already on shooting chat and
вот я уже на стреляя в чат и
spam subscriber to kilo channel to
спам подписчица на килограмм канал чтоб
relax subscribed to dishes
расслабьтесь подписаны к блюдам
develop 5 grams channel and let's
развивать 5 грамм канал и давайте
share
поделимся
porsche porsche and video 6  we
porsche porsche и видеоролик 6 у нас
will have three chatroulette points today to
будут три chatroulette очки сегодня там
multiply there and I
размножаться и я
move today above 20 million not only to
move сегодня выше 20 млн не то чтобы
record roulette aliya
записать рулетку алия
mih mih
мих мих
hears you stream chapcha stream chan poison
слышит вас стрима чапче стрим чан яд
is called without you from Rome you
называется без того чтоб от рима ты нас
water us and let 2 thousand hh there in the
воды и пустил 2 тыс hh там на
Kharkiv region happened for  Russians with checks,
харьковщине произошло за россиян чеками
put a plus sign who wants to
поставьте плюсик кто хочет подавайте
submit today's rozmov from Russians with checks
сегодняшнюю розмова з россиян чекам про
about how things are in the Kharkiv region and we
то как там дела харьковской области и
take
беремся
this something behind I am from Ukraine, the city of
это что-то позади я из украины город
Khmelnitsky and where exactly is Lenitsky,
хмельницким и откуда именно леницкий это
where is yaesu kvn, the city of Khmelnitsky
где вообще yaesu квн город хмельницкого
from the Russian city, I am from the Krasnodar
из российского города я из краснодарский
Territory on  I love the city of Novorossiysk,
край на город новороссийска
I will be closed, so I’m more of these
я обожаю буду замкнут вот я побольше эти
moments when the participants have at least something
моменты когда участники хоть что-то у
back there, this is where he is from and
тебя там сзади это вообще откуда он и
still, kids like now I’m there a crest
все-таки детки типа сейчас я там хохла
on the go, but bleach attacks would have whole you, she’s a
на ходу но bleach атаки бы целые вас она
horse, traffic rules, since we’re like that  all the same, there is a
лошадь пдд раз мы так и все таки есть
port yes yes yes, look at the audi from
портовый да да да вот смотрите audi из
Russia, I ask how you feel about the
россии спрашиваю как вы относитесь к
fact that the
тому что
Ukrainian Ukrainian army is
украинская украинская армия проводит де
demilitarizing Russian  troops in ukraine
милитаризацию российских войск в украине
and the
и
moscow region, yes, i doubt that
московском районе да я сомневаюсь что
she is spending
она проводит
tell us with russia went out in
расскажите у нас с россией поехал out у
my military city, that is, well,
меня в городе военной то есть ну стоят
they’re standing plus overtook a part of us, two parts of the airborne troops
плюс настиг часть у нас две части вдв
went and
шла и
the naval unit we have, they are
военно-морская часть у нас они
half staffed,
наполовину укомплектована
little went to  ukraine up to 150 thousand
мало поехала в украину до 150 тысяч
as far as israel 200 and why so few were
насколько израиль 200 а почему так мало
sent to ukraine that they now
отправили в украину что они теперь
get run away shameful from ukraine
получают убегают позорные из украины
died run away we didn’t run further
погибли убегают мы дальше по не убегали
why this dream zone is falling this ours
почему зону этот сон падают этот наш
let’s start up to the kharkiv region
давайте начнем до харьковская область
so Ukraine has already been liberated analysis
так уже освобождена украины анализ
wait for the troops yourself  you went there,
обожди на войска сами туда ушли
did you understand the
вы поняли
Kharkov Kharkov region was not
харьковская харьковская область не
liberated, the troops themselves left from there, so the
освобождена войска сами оттуда ушли так
Hitler of these
гитлер этих
persons and
лиц и
can say yes, we are
может сказать да мы просто
just liberating Borodin, you are
она написана бородина вы
liberated, just wait for the truth, the
освобождены обожди на правда нет
concept is liberated extensible
освобождена понятие растяжимое
video, wait a minute, I saw a video, for example, where
ролик погоди я видел ролик например где
you don’t wear it honestly  ukraine
вашего тут не носи честно украина янте
yante politically that ukraine was not particularly
политично что украина особо не
interested don’t tell me why  not
интересовало не расскажи почему это не
liberation, here is the flight of the Russian
освобождение вот бегство российских
troops, why is there no snow of the countries to the
войск почему это нет снега стран к
flight, the flight, yes, ours have already reached the
бегство бегство да уже наши вышли на
border to Russia from the Belgorod
границу до россии из белгородской
region,
области ну
why did
почему
I watch a shorter report, it’s you there, a
я смотрел короче репортаж это вас там
soldier from the advanced warner in the spring,
солдата с передовой варнер весной он
why is he going to the Wagner, he said that, well, the infantry
чего к вагнера он говорил что ну пехота
went there  50000 people so that the Ukrainian
там пошла 50000 человек чтобы украинском
type we don’t have so many to
типа у нас такого количества нету чтобы
defend but against them and therefore were
оборонять но против них и поэтому были
forced to retreat why why did
as вынуждена отступать а почему почему
Russia put so few people that it was
россия так мало людей поставила что
forced to retreat from the Ukrainian infantry
вынужден от украинские пехоты отступать
when
когда
it teaches its version of the plague flower and in
она научить свою версию чуму цветок и по
Russia they have one and a half million  army
россии там у них полтора миллиона армия
they sent a few people and in the car
они послали немножко людей да и в машине
now retreat from the Ukrainian infantry
теперь отступать от украинской пехоты
write your version what this young man will say now
напишите свою версию что сейчас скажет
why Russia has such a huge army and they
почему у россии такая огромная армия а
sent there to Ukraine just a
послали туда в украину всего лишь
little bit that against 50 thousand
немножечко что против 50 тысяч
Ukrainian infantry she could not resist
украинской пехоты она не смогла устоять
why they couldn’t  could
почему они не могли
60,000 Russian army put 100,000
60000 русской армии поставит 100000
interesting
интересно
so few people I don't  I know every
так мало людей я не знаю каждый
leader
руководитель
look now now they come and the
смотрите сейчас сейчас приходят и
Ukrainians will come further and everyone will
украинской дальше по придет и все будете
depart the labor of a couple on the territory of Russia
отходите труда пара на территории россии
that he or maybe on the territory of Russia I
что ему а может и на территории россии я
don’t if you call on the territory of Russia
не если вы зовете на территории россии
it will be a mobilization of a declaration of war and
это будет мобилизации объявления войны и
[ __ ] the red
трахают ковровой
carpet one witness of the carpet
дорожке один свидетель ковровых
bombings  and a witness for five years in
бомбардировок и свидетеля пять лет для
order for the carpet bombing to
того чтобы ковровой бомбардировки надо
take place so that your pilots are not afraid to fly into
чтобы ваши летчики не боялись залетать в
the Ukrainian zone of action and
зону действия украинского а
from the pilots are afraid to fly in why the carpet bombing
из летчики боятся залетать почему ракету
is still flying
до сих пор летают
somewhere, but somewhere not,
ковровые бомбардировки нет а где-то нет
I ask you say they are afraid to fly the
я спрашиваю говорите боятся залетать
missile from where they fly from
ракета от откуда откуда летают они
where and what do we need from the Caspian to something
откуда и что нам из каспийского чему-то
Caspian, but how many of these
каспийского ну а сколько этих
far, far swamps of nature
дальнее-дальнее болото природе
worked part of the work part to
срабатывали часть работы часть
skip naturally it is
пропускать естественно она она
similar to how ours bomb Belgorod Crimea there
аналогична как наши бомбят там крым
until the summer part you shoot down
белгорода до лета часть вы сбиваете
part no Crimea Crimea no
часть нет крым крыму нет
shot was dinner two shots soon
выстрела был обед два выстрела скоро
fit 1 2 3 types
подойдет 1 2 3 типа
definitely knocked out wait  let's not
обязательно выбили подождите давайте не
have to if you hit the Crimea every
должна если бы вы били по крыму каждый
day, as you say, why we
день как вы говорите почему у нас людей
didn’t evacuate people from there, get married there,
оттуда не эвакуировали замуж там живут
go to work,
ходят на работу
buy it, inspect
покупается досмотрите потому что потому
because Ukraine, unlike your
что украина в отличие от вашей
fascist federation, doesn’t bomb the
фашистской федерации так она не бомбит
civilian population like that, we’ll fill
мирное население набьем
it with a fan  she hits military
фанат она бьёт она бьет по военным
targets in which the Moravian fascist doesn’t hit the
объектам в чем фашист моравский не бью
Russians are hitting non-military
повален русские бьют не по военными по
civilians until they beat fedoras cashmere, and
гражданским до лупят fedoras кашемир а
this one in Kharkov that you announced
этот в харькове который вы озвучили то
that the military facility does not have a
что военный объект нет у
barbie light and left the maternity hospitals
барби свет и оставили родильные дома
and there is a
да там
hospital cinema for people a  abandoned and
больнице кино для людей а заброшка а
Zaporizhzhya from whom it is possible to bomb
запорожского из кто бомбит можно
Russians Russians the Russian army
россияне россияне русская армия там
stands there and bada itself in order to, yes, to
стоит и сама себя bada для того да для
blame Ukraine for this, of
того чтобы украину обвинять в этом
course, to blame Ukraine for yes, in the same place, the magate
конечно обвинять в да там же магатэ
dawn sending higher damn it saw how
рассвет отправляя выше блин видел как
rich it was told why such a
она богата рассказали почему такая
trajectory because the rocket was going  with
траектория потому что ракета шла с
kuklin and but before entering she
куклин и но она перед заходом
turned around there serge already from 8 to 17
развернулась там сержа ли уже с 8 по 17
it’s not we who didn’t save which cat you are  some
это не мы не спасали которые вы которые
gta tried to explain why the trajectory of the
gta пытались объяснить почему траектории
rocket did not see such a look, yes,
ракеты не видел такого посмотрите да
watch the video, you know which portable where
посмотри видео знаешь какой portable где
Lucy Orestovich said that
люси орестович говорила что
on May 9 we will dance a zucchini in the Kremlin, I
9 мая будем в кремле кабачок танцевать я
adore the theme of cola, undermining the view of
обожение темы колы у них подрывая вид
Orestovich to know Orestovich, but I asked
орестович знать орестович зато к прошил
the woman for the length of the barrel of the symbol seriously
к бабой на длина ствола символа серьезно
none of us directly, but for whether they are so dull
никто нас прямо а для мутко ли их так
undermining the shorter twisted brother-in-law says
подрывая короче витого шурин говорит
it was the seals on them that the wenger passed
именно печати на них верить прошла
and
wenger и
his task was able to task Orestovich and
его задача смогли задача орестович а
lean on doing absolutely right
наваливайся заниматься абсолютно верно
absolutely right task
абсолютно верно задача
see the task task Orestovich however I
смотри задача задача орестович однако я
didn’t panic violated that’s all yes panic
не паникую нарушил вот и все да панику
with a knife  panic, but I said about the zucchini,
ножом паникой а вот я сказал про кабачок
believe me, I’ll say yes, because your
это поверь я скажу да потому что у вас
farts are undermined by this, you
от этого подрываются пердаки вот вы
see, you are talking about Orestovich, you
видите вы говорите про орестович вы
think about Orestovich, you are
думаете про орестович вы
Orestovich Orestovich, he does not work for
орестович орестович он работает не на
our audience, she is yours, he will shower
нашу аудиторию она ваши он закидает
absolutely correct
абсолютно правильные
messenger on someone  then laughs in here
мессенджером на кто-то смеется в тут
points out the truth hello these I don’t know who is
очкует правда привет этих не знаю кто
nice I know d
приятно я знаю да и вид а теперь после
and now, after you got from Kharkov to the maps, you got Dathan’s star in the Kharkov region, you don’t need to get slower on the wheel, that is, eight thousand of your goals is 880 really 88 you are Varna for there in from 80 to 800 if to our Konashenkov listen, so there is already a lawn 200 long ago correctly, I don’t care how the food and the points are not bloody pros about if, after all, 800 there 800000 you already beat so many infantry there, look you kill so much the arrival of Russia, not so much kill the infantry, but still you don’t have enough see the explanation if you have killed so many Ukrainian infantry so how can you hold the front that you are running away from the Ukrainian infantry we are running away from the infantry we are all areas I don’t understand when you are well museum awakened disk space it’s on close quarters, but for the sake of sleep, on the development, pour experience and in the Kyiv region of Sumy, we moved away, this is mine, I have Kent, a contract soldier, here he is  now I’ve arrived on vacation algorithms
вот он сейчас приехал в отпуск алгоритмы
how they went in there without a fight and left without
как зашли туда без боя так и вышли без
why dads came out [ __ ] there that’s
почему вышли папы пиздюли там вот а
why they gave the order because
почему дали приказ потому заболевали
they got sick to change their mind from if not wait I
передумать от если нет подожди у меня
have such logic and give [ __ ] the army
логика такая есть и дают [__] армия
runs away the body just entered the city walks
убегает органа просто зашла город ходит
without a fight to get life  at lirene das auto
без боя получать жизнь у lirene das auto
club then explanatory interesting
club тогда объяснительных интересная
khachkars why the Russian army did something
хачкары почему российская армия что-то
goodwill gesture departed and spat
жест доброй воли сделала отошла и спатки
its sums Chernihiv voluntarily
его сумм чернигова добровольно так
sank its cruisers so they
потопила свои крейсера
said of a specific ethnicity they are like the
сказал конкретной этнической они как
Sumy region yes why they
сумская область да почему они оттуда
technically departed from there good life adding
технически отошли жизнь добрый добавив
yes why a cruiser  I’ll drown a trash as a
да почему а крейсер мусорного утону как
gesture of goodwill, why yes, why from
жест доброй воли ну почему да почему из
this
этого
snake island how kind you can
острова змеиный как же добрый можете
sit down you can’t change why why,
садиться не можете изменить зачем зачем
well, that’s right, therefore I’m saying
ну вот правильно поэтому я же говорю
if you are why we need him dreaming of a
если вы почему нам нужны ему снится
dog why we need to fight on him,
собачей зачем нам надо сражаться на него
but this is your territory  why why
но это же ваша территория зачем почему
didn’t they strategically landed for what what
не высадили стратегически для чего что
what but above it was reduced there about how  some
что но выше сводили там про какие-то
records didn’t reach the bottom, so why are
записи не долетали до низа же так зачем
they standing there golden near Odessa
там золотистом стоят возле одессы
it arose why restoration, but
возникало его зачем восстановление но
why don’t you want to tell him it
почему бы не вы хотите говорим ему
controls or work on the withdrawal,
контролирует или работы по выводу
look from there you ran away now you
смотрите оттуда вы убежали теперь вы
ran away ran away and ran away if
убежали бежали и бежали убежали если
I see yes why don’t you  can you
увижу да почему вы не можете вы теперь
now why among
теперь зачем среди
that dude in all seriousness we
тот чувак на полном серьезе к же мы мы
didn’t run away our own snake so
не убегали собственного змеиной так
why because you are printed there you
почему потому что вы там печатные вы
can feed in that forest our
сожете питания в том лесу наше
command
командование
rune tattoo why should we strategically
руны тату для чего нам стратегического
plant there so and that we will be there
туда высаживать так и что мы будем там
in no way but  so we ourselves think de paja until the
никак а так сами думаем de paja до
very kalaev this dude knows he
самого калаев этот чувак знает он равен
gave them equal and the star
им дал и звездюлей
vanych was appointed to the snake got
ваныч назначили на змеиной получил
seen this day and we didn’t
видели этот день и мы оттуда не
liberate the territory from there they also hear
освободили территорию доносятся тоже не
you can’t you want
может вы хотите
to land on a dish and why should we
на блюдо высаживаться а зачем нам там
stand there I don’t know why  you went there
стоять вот не знаю а зачем туда зашли
so you ask me from the Minister of
так вы меня спрашивать у министра
Defense, well, probably not, you’re just so
обороны ну наверное нет вы просто так
awesome, everything means they didn’t run
офигенно все значит они не убежали
away, maybe you have  there is something else
отошли может у вас есть кое-то пацан еще
that I love numbers so much, he knows
который я так люблю цифры сущим знает
icloud, they can see that he knew how to know about and
icloud им что видно умел знаем о и у
he’s aiming to sort everything out, I’m the
него целен все разбирать я с ними
Minister of Defense with them, I turn it on in short,
министр обороны я короче включает
I’m just the guys I’ll say here I
я просто я вот мужики скажу тут
turn on the air conditioner, turn it off,
кондиционером типа включаю выключаю
take into account, I’m trying on the island  the serpentine was
учетом на пытаюсь на острове змеиный был
also understand, he will tell you the doctor
тоже понимаете он вам расскажет мне врач
and the acquaintance to see
а знакомый досмотреть
me is just somehow very interesting a
меня просто как-то очень интересно
series of the same goodwill news from the
череда вот этих же вестей доброй воли с
Kiev Chernihiv and Sumy region at
киевской черниговской и сумской областью
no cost below the will agree the
без затрат ниже воли согласен
cruiser moscow drowned 0 well, in the morning they
крейсер москва утонул 0 ну и утром с
kicked the serpentine island for now
острова змеиный выгнали на сейчас из
I was already expelled from Kharkiv region from Kherson region, I’m already
харьковщины выгнали с херсонщины уже
pressing it, it’s you who expel me, it’s a juicy team to
дожимаю это вы меня это команде сочный
expel if it was as it was and it’s worth it, and
выгонять если она как была так и стоит а
where it was, it’s worth seeing and the
где как было то стоит посмотреть и
village is freed to the right, well,
освобождается села до направо ну
for example, that the city entered at one o’clock at its
например что город вошли в час у неё в
base,
основе
I’ll say this to the city two  the day before they
я скажу так в город два дня до того как
fell down was there anything else they said you would
свалились было то ли еще что говорили вы
enter the city you would enter the raisins you would enter you spoke
в город войдете в изюм войдет у говорил
for soon yours spoke for no matter how much
за скоро ваша говорили за сколько ни аж
and so the floor lamps are the
и так торшеры
key  turn out no one said yes
ключевой оказаться никто не говорил да
not to the sick and the ivate bravura stage in the
не на больных и этап ивате бравуре в
balakleya are held there by the Russian
балаклея держатся там российские
Samara cathedral gives strength there the battle
самарских собор дает силу там боя не
will not recede
будет отступать
[laugh]
[смех]
why
не болеть пропаганда на то почему
look literally in a matter of days
смотрите буквально за считанные дни
it was glue kupyansk raisins how
повалилась было клея купянск изюм как
it happened and then it
это так получилось и дальше так
happened but it’s very,
получилось но очень-очень это можно
very easy to explain to the foresters you have
очень просто объясни лесничим у вас
private military companies which countries are
частные военные компании каких стран
now located, I don’t know at all, but I
сейчас находятся это вообще не знаю а
know what the commander is on our
знаю чего командира находится у нас на
in front of there is none of our side sochi will become
перед нет ни нашей стороны сочи станет
your company page yes no
вашей странице компании находится да нет
your camura is from yours there and
вашего камура же из вашего же там и
all sorts of foreign private companies
всякие иностранные частные компании
scania you used to
scania у вас раньше добровольцами
come with volunteers from you military
приезжаешь с у вас приезжают военными
company I understand that it turns out that
компанию я понял то есть получается это
you are allocating snow to the yard there are names
вам выделение снега во двор там имена
who is this Ukrainian is, it turns out that it’s for
кто это украинца есть получается это вам
you that the star gave you just not the
это вам звездюлей дала просто не
Ukrainian army, but foreign  strange military
украинская армия а иностранный военный
com what does it have to do with it from our side
com при чём тут это с нашей стороны
went all your thousands there
поехала ступит все тысяч ваших там
more than a million booleans it turns out
больше миллиона рублей булевы получается
more than six months you can’t get
больше полугода не можете вернуть назад
yours back keep Ruffalo someone is working
своих держите руффало кого-то получается
and now we are already returning numerical
и сейчас мы уже вернуть численное
superiority
превосходство
and why and why the Russians will adjust
а почему а почему россияне подгонит
numerical superiority to  they didn’t kill
численное превосходство чтобы не убивали
yours, these in the minority,
ваших вот этих в меньшинстве
no floor is superfluous to me, we
никакой этаж не ко мне вопрос лишними не
won’t say there you, that is, you
станем говоришь там вы вы то есть ты
somehow interpret, and when I ask you, I’m
как-то трактуют а когда тебя спрашиваю я
not so much because I know that the
не столько образом потому что я знаю что
army went there, not in full force, there is a
поехала армия не в полном составе туда
clan with us  an army of over one and a half
клан у нас армия свыше полутора
million people went to 150 thousand,
миллионов человек на а поехала 150 тысяч
plus a private war, the company
плюс частная война компания в
organized to their people there, honestly,
организацию к их там человек вам честно
I don’t know, that is, well, how much, well,
я не зна то есть ну это сколько ну дак
I find 50,000, I really understand that
нахожу 50000 я правда понимаю что у
Ukraine has more troops and that’s why she
украины войск больше да и поэтому она на
kicked out in the Kharkiv region, yes  I’m not saying anything, but
харьковщине выгнала да я ничего не а
I’m telling the truth that this war has been there for a long time,
правду я говорю что эта война есть пор
there are defeats, there are victories, that’s all, then
есть поражение есть победы вот и все то
in the Kharkov region, then defeat before
в харьковской области то разгром до
the Russian army was, I think it’s a shame a
российской армии был я считаю это позор
shame on absolutely because to [ __ ] the
позор на абсолютно потому что просрать
territory like that with knowing for
так территорию с причем заведомо зная за
10 I don’t know what else 10 days before all
10 не знаю что еще за 10 дней до всех
these events they said that there would be
этих событий говорили о том что будет
an attack on Kharkov even in the
гонки наступление на харьков даже в
telegram channels of the bed this is how they
telegram каналах постели это как они
leaked  I don’t know why I don’t know the
просочились я не знаю почему не знаю
most normal adequate explanation,
самое нормальное адекватное объяснение
they pissed away, they were simply undermined, but don’t you think that this series is about gray or an opening, it will expand, I don’t know the time yet, for whom look from the armor, the forces of Ukraine have already
смотрите с брони силы украины уже
occupied Svetogorsk Yes, well, and what else  that
светогорск заняли да ну и что ну еще то
is, they are already entering the Luhansk region again,
есть уже на луганщину входят снова как
how does it turn out,
так получается
look if you send a small
смотрите если вы отправлю туда маленькое
number of troops there such silence cook rush
количество войск такая тишь кук ринемся
now to grind from your soldiers
сейчас перемолоть от ваших солдатиков
why they won’t send the whole army lower life
почему не пошлют всю армию нижняя жизнь
I’m alive the first I don’t know all these how its
я жива первых не знаю всех этих как его
subtleties are there and what sent what
тонкости которые там а что отправили что
sent how much to the sender maybe there is a
послали сколько до шлют может быть там
whale there are plans only I don’t know it at this
кита планы есть лишь не знаю это в это
time will show you understand about it now
время покажет понимаете об этом сейчас
su  it’s difficult to read until time shows,
судить сложно пока время ли не покажет
that is, when you are interested in something, you
то есть когда вам что-то интересно вы
judge
судите
no, now you’re not saying correctly, I judge
нет сейчас не правильно говоришь я сужу
by the moment that has already passed, that
по тем моментом который уже прошли то
is, they don’t go there, but have already passed, so
есть они не идут там а уже прошли вот я
I serve them, and what will happen in the future  I
по ним служу а то что будет в будущем я
don’t know, you can say it will be tomorrow,
ж не знаю ты можешь сказать будет завтра
I can’t say tomorrow it
я не могу можем могу сказать завтра
will be convenient tomorrow Wednesday, well, in your
будет удобно завтра среда ну вот в твоей
life, something will change there, did you know it will change, I
жизни что-то там изменится ли так знали
will become one day older,
сменится стану на один день старше
you will become one older, but this is the
станешь на один старше но это
only thing that can happen not  I can
единственное что может произойти не могу
say the sun you can you stand from a
сказать солнце ты можешь ты стоишь с
point with an accuracy to say for sure
точки с точностью до наверняка сказать
that you can walk down the street tomorrow a
что ты можешь завтра идти по улице
brick on your head with an accuracy for sure
кирпич на голову с точностью наверняка
no one can say anything god the
никто ничего не может сказать бог тоже
same but come a certain probability
самое а приди определенная вероятность
for example 2 so with a certain degree of
например 2 итак с определенной долей
probability we can state that
вероятности мы можем констатировать что
tomorrow russia will not be able to do anything
завтра россия не сможет ничего сделать
in the kharkiv region will not be able to do anything
на харьковщине не сможет ничего сделать
i can’t say i’m not sure i don’t know
я не могу сказать я не уверен я не знаю
how i know maybe that it will be
откуда знаю может быть что она будет
tomorrow and  the day after tomorrow I worked in the
завтра и послезавтра себя работал в
Ministry of Defense there in the same way
министерстве обороны там точно также
to give you what to do if you were the
давать чтобы ты сделал если ты был
Ministry of Defense what you did
министерстве обороны чтоб ты сделал
to win this war of Ukrainians to
чтобы выиграть эту войну украинцев
win then first of all I would
выиграть то во первых я бы в
first of all find out why go there
перво-наперво узнал зачем туда идти это
at the first moment why and
в первый момент зачем и
morons taught and reason  no, and that before
[__] поучал и разуме нет и что перед
having a pipe, you need it for yes, you
имевший трубы ты треба за да ты себе
found food for yourself on hiba ballistas to ukraine
питания на хиба нашли баллисты в украину
on hiba pacino you are a special operation so and so
на хиба пачино ты спецоперацию так и так
on here for the pie from these pacino and
дальше тут за пирог у данных пачино и
income, then the chopper is on this
доходы то чоппер этим як
side and how damn it
стороне и как блин это
if there was a danger then
если бы была опасность тогда бы
accordingly, I would have acted harshly,
соответственно я бы действовал жестко
because we’ll
они так как наши там
work out chatter there, chatter, talk
позанимаюсь болтовней размусоливать
about an accident, and so on and so
рассусоливать дтп и так далее и тому
forth, if I think I’ve gone, then
подобное если я считаю себе пошел то
I should already act tough without
надо уже действовать жестко без всяких
any chatter of conversations about plans for the
там болтовни разговоров планов на
future, these ideas should be done, and if not, I
будущее эти идеи делать а если не и не
wasn’t going to go  then nothing at all, so
собирался идти то ничего вообще вот так
what is the goal of all this here is what should be
какая цель все это вот что должно быть в
what should be the victory of Russia in
чем должна заключаться победа россии в
ukraine what should it be
украине в чем она должна быть
for  fixed what should happen to
зафиксирован что должно случиться чтобы
say about everything russia defeated him and over
сказать о все россия победила его и над
said we don’t say anything at all the
сказали ничего не говорим вообще тем
more I’ll say when it all started in
больше скажу когда это все началось в
his heart if you start talking
его сердце если у становитесь говорить
frankly because no one knew anything about
откровенно потому что никто ничего об
it no one suspected anything
этом не знал никто ничего не подозревал
here erase yourself and go  I’m
тут стирать себе и пошли я же я же
let’s say I’m a civilian, I’m
допустим я же гражданский человек я же
not a military man, how can I know what and
не военный откуда я могу знать там что и
how I just woke up on February 24, I found out
как я просто проснулся 24 февраля узнал
that Russian troops entered the
что российские войска зашли на
territory of Ukraine, a meat grinder began
территорию украины началась мясорубка
work for everyone, look, here’s what
работы всем смотри вот у меня вот то что
I’m saying about a friend  which is the sum of
я те говорю про знакомого который сумму
me,
меня
he’s them like this, he didn’t talk about
он их вот как вот он не рассказывала о
them being sent to the Kursk region to the
их отправили в курскую область на
training ground allegedly and then just quickly without
полигон якобы а потом просто быстро не
saying anything people who and where they threw them into
говоря ничего чел кого и куда кинули на
the squirrel’s territory right before reaching the
территорию белка прям вот не доехав до
piece and then the food horn is not an automatic machine
куска и потом питание рожок не автомат
two horns then  they even have a really
два рожка то есть они даже толком
charged sky and transfer it to the
заряженные небо и перебросить на
territory of Ukraine as he talked about
территории украины это как рассказывал о
and then, respectively, when everything had already
а потом уже соответственно когда уже все
come to that h  then they said that there would be a
дошло до того что сказали что будет
war config with Ukraine and threw it out
войны конфиг с украиной и выкинули
first we wait then threw it into the amount of
сначала мы ждем потом кинули в сумму
sums he stood for a month then the troops
сумах он простоял месяц потом войска
were withdrawn on March 29 now he arrived here
вывели 29 марта сейчас он приехал вот
like a vacation for an hour for a month we will
как типа отпуском час на месяц внесем
bring if unwillingness to return
если нежелание возвращаться
unwillingness to return not to
нежелание насчет возвращаться не
return here I am with him when
возвращаться вот я с ним когда
he was talking when he came on
разговаривал когда вот он приезжал в
vacation, he just came to visit us himself,
отпуск он просто к нам гости приехал сам
he lives in this Nizhny Novgorod region
он живет в этом нижегородской области
jeans city, he said that
джинсы городе он сказал что пол давить
it was necessary to press the floor, by the way, he was also on cleanups in
надо он кстати еще был на зачистки в
Mariupol, he smashed it for what he is
мариуполе разнесла ради чего вот он он
ready to go there to get banged for
готов туда ехать чтобы его грохнули ради
what  here are the parents, what is the purpose of this war
чего вот родители какая цель этой войны
in ukraine
в украине
no, i can’t tell you about
нет я не могу тебе сказать по поводу
it for the purposes of statehood, but
того в целях государственности но вот
when I talked to him when he was
когда я с ним разговаривал когда он был
here, he said something that at least I saw
здесь он сказал что-то что хоть я видел
mariupol how these, as he said,
мариуполе как эти как он сказал
Ukrainian creatures guide were spent  [ __ ] the
украинские твари гайд тратились [__] за
people, he meant the Azov people, and so
людьми это он имел ввиду азовцев и так
on, he was on the cleansing of these, that
далее он был на зачистки вот этих вот то
is, it turns out he was part of those
есть получается он был в составе тех
troops who  who bombed Mariupol, peaceful,
войск которые бомбили мариуполь мирный
not a round of infantry entering to
не раунда составе пехоты заходящий на
clean up the city, yes, that is, but it is
зачистку города да то есть но это в
part of the entire troops of the Russian army
составе всего войск российской армии
that bombed Mariupol, which
которые бомбила мариуполь которая
destroyed Mariupol, yes, that is, people, and
уничтожила мариуполь да то есть люди и
why only for some reason did he say something wrong,
почему только он почему-то говорить не
he didn’t drag it again before  this
так не потащил еще раз до того как этот
fool came to ukraine right now why is he a
дурак пришел в украину счас почему он
fool, but double skin is much more and drinking down, they
дурак но двойных кожа гораздо и запивая
give an order, you saw him carry out the
слышите выдают приказ ты ему выполнять
servicemen, a fool who
усмотрел военнослужащие дура который
doesn’t even know the purpose of the operation, the character
даже не знает цели операции характере
can become for the sake of what he
может стать ради чего ради чего он
dies for, is he ready
умирает на еще он готов ли ты служил
for  what with the orcs
орбит нет вот ради чего с орками армией
army when asked why or the [ __ ] they will
на вопрос зачем или на хера тебе скажут
tell you so they told you to do there, that is
вот тебе сказали ты делать там то есть
, a month has already passed so the state is
вот уже проходит месяц так государство
not a citizen and she is scared our mixture
не гражданин и она напугана наша смесь
turns out to be non-citizens there is no one
получается не граждане имеется никто не
understands why, that is, they tell you to
понимает зачем зачем то есть вам говорят
go, we won’t
иди дух не
bomb the spirit  and we are told these debts are
разбомбим и нам говорят эти долги
inherently so it will turn out I can tell the
неотъемлемо так получатся я могу сказать
meter listen I can how I cannot
метра слушай я могу как я не могу
speak for everything  of the state, I can
говорить за все государства я могу
speak specifically for myself and this reflects
сказать конкретно за себя и это отражает
my position as a whole custom from everything
мою позицию в целом кастом от всего того
that is happening now and in general if you
что происходит сейчас и в целом если вы
came to my house, let's say I live
ко мне пришли домой вот я допустим живу
in Krasnodar nra and now I would come to
в краснодарском нра и вот пришел бы к
me, let's say the Ukrainian army said to my
мне допустим армия украины на мою
territory  there it will be our
территорию сказала там это будет нашей
land, I would go and go cut them all
земле я бы пошел пошел бы их всех
out here is my opinion the water of everything
вырезать вот мое мнение воду всего того
that is happening just look what
что происходит просто смотри что
happens then this is your friend so he saw
получаться то это твой друг так он видел
what Mariupol turned into before
что во что превратился мариуполь до
this blooming colorful city and he
этого цветущий красочный город так и он
does not even understand why this is  and
даже не понимает зачем это и
now he will continue to be given an order, he
сейчас ему дальше будут давать приказ он
will go to follow the order like a fool
как дурак будет идти выполнять приказ
at night, whether he will be there or not, this is a big
ночью там будет или не будет это большой
question, this is the second time he will not know that
вопрос это раз во вторых не узнает что
here and then he is not afraid, he is no
тут и дальше он не боится он уже нет он
longer in doubt, he just has a vacation until
не сомневается у него просто отпуск до
October 15, we  do not recall him yet and
15 октября мы его пока не отзывать и
signs he has now gone to do home repairs
знамений он сейчас поехал делать ремонт
okay well thanks for the conversation
окей хорошо спасибо за разговор
artist yes yes put likes I will see you
художник да да ставьте лайки буду вас
when I was here in short
когда бывал тут короче 600 людей лайки в
300 let’s put likes and you’ll be and a
300 давайте да ставьте лайки и будешь и
tape measure today in such triremes of branches
рулеточка сегодня в таких триер ветки
like eyebrows to feed the threads
так виде бровками кормить-то нитки на не
weren’t just dodik keys just well, woodpecker
были просто додики keys просто ну дятлу
uncle here, roll it’s tight it’s important yes
дядя тут вот катитесь поджаты важно да
put likes and let’s run, yes, in order to
ставьте лайки и побежим да вот в
achieve it, the soldiers, the husband said typical
добиться он солдаты муж сказали типовую
and you, well, tick, she defended her signature on the right,
и вы так ну тикать она справа защищали
and on the
свою подпись и на
throttle of the krine whom the banter is so trying to
дросселе крине кого стеба так пытаться
freaks Ivan and does not think later
чудики иван и не задумывается позже
butt in the army so it's all in the
приклад в армии так это все у
rumor it's
слух это
me it's a piece of paper at home as such this and who
я я это бумажку дома таковым этом и кто
to sign the Ukrainian people next what
подписаться украинский народ далее что
petri matt wants  and donate the axis and
хочет петри мэтт и донатом оси и
messages, I will fix her leg before
послания я ее закреплю ногу до
jumping out,
выскакивать
I forgot 6 20 donations, but the documents of
я 6 забылся 20 доната а вот документы
the Ministry of Internal Affairs mentioned so ok, I’ll scatter my friend
мвд упоминали так окей за раскидаю друга
roulette
рулеточка
gd about such a topic, like the
gd про такую тему як
national narrowest house,
национальный самый узкий дом ай
oh yes, who
да кому
will have to if in Russian now
предстоит если вот по-русски сейчас
I’ll say now there will be a topic  about national
скажу сейчас будет тема про национальное
self-
самосознание
consciousness, if people from
вот если нас будут смотреть люди из
Tatarstan from Russia watch us, then maybe you will
татарстана из россии так может вам будет
not be very pleased with what you
не совсем приятно от того что вы
hear from a person  and with whom there will be a
услышите от человека на с которым будет
conversation now,
сейчас беседа
let's pudding yourself
давайте пудинг сам
your gender russia
ваш пол россия священная
our sacred state
наша держава
[music]
[музыка]
if I go to ukraine there the
если меня в украину там
center is
центр
on k starting from the floor it’s
на к начиная с полом не
not beautiful you can sing at least a
в это красиво пели можете допеть хотя бы
couple of couplets, otherwise you sang two lines
пару куплетов а то вон две строчки спели
and the purchase didn’t even  managed that you don’t know don’t
а купля даже не успели что не знаете не
take it off in short,
снимай кароче у них
what is your center called Ukraine you are
как у вас центр называется украине вы же
Ukrainian no I’m from Lithuania
украинец нет я из литвы
from someone else’s Ukrainian theme for I didn’t
от чужой украинская тема за не
like the flag to
понравился флаг
sleep and sleep and at least one verse of the soul
спать и спать и хотя бы один куплет души
I have not yet met a single Russian
я еще не встретил ни одного русского
who Vladimir Putin is well done  let's
который владимир путин молодец давайте
be shy what it was at first so
чем застеснялись что такое сначала такой
impudent were it I calmly looked at you
дерзкий были это я спокойно на вас
didn't react badly and you were
смотрел не реагировал плохо и вы
shy I can be impudent always
застеснялись я могу быть дерзким всегда
runs away and doesn't run away let's you are
убегает и не убегаю давайте давайте вы
very, very easy to
очень-очень легко поддаетесь
manipulate this is an interesting pulse no
манипуляциям это интересный пульса нет
I don't give in seriously at all to the side that is
не поддаюсь серьезно вообще боку то есть
you are a man, well, put a plus sign who
вы человек а ну поставьте плюсик кто
respects 100 to clap and is easy to
уважает 100 хлопать и даётся легко
manipulate, and minus who respects they
манипуляциям а минус кто уважает они
are still personal income tax one is not cotton bullets plus
все-таки ндфл одному не пуль ваты плюс
if you think that this guy is very
если вы считаете что этим парнем очень
easy to manipulate, and minus if he is
легко манипулировать а минус если он
difficult to manipulate when not
сложно поддается манипуляция при не
amenable to manipulation at all yes,
поддаётся манипуляциям вообще да
go nuts, I met the first person in the
[__] я встретил первого человека в
world who is not amenable to
мире который вообще не поддаются
manipulation at all, like to count and manipulate
манипуляциям типа на кол и манипулируют
psychologists say that everyone is amenable to
психологи говорят что все поддаются
manipulation and me and you a  here you don’t
манипуляциям и я и вы а вот вы не
succumb to manipulating sheep
поддаетесь от манипулирует овцы
learn very quickly yes tell me to
обучайтесь очень быстро да скажи мне
learn
обучаться
I’m from ukraine the city of khmelnitsky and you are
я из украины город хмельницкий а вы
from kazan kazan and tatar
откуда
in fact yes and the
по сути да а
other 50 km
другие 50 км
from the forehead and
со лба и
sprat troubles you
кильки troubles you
tatar was mom mom and tangerine
татарин был мама мама и мандарином
dolboyeb  lan without jokes then darina 50
[__] лан без шуток то дарина 50
percent because mom is tatar
процентов потому что мама татарка
pack tatar as if mom is tatar dad
пак татарин как если мама татарка папа
tatar as it is written 50 percent
татарин как бы написано 50 процентов
living for now if you are one hundred
живущий пока что если вы на сто
percent tatar
процентов татарин
i will be when i am 90 it will
буду когда мне 90 будет
be but look here you are by the way
это а вот смотрите вот вы мне кстати
interesting to me the days are very serious  when
интересно дни очень серьезно когда людей
I meet people from national republics, I am
из национальных республик встречаю мне
always interested to hear why they
всегда интересно послушать почему они
support the industry  and the first thing you did was
поддерживают в отрасли вы первым делом
we started singing the anthem of Russia, don’t
мы начали петь гимн россии вот не
look online, you caught it, but
смотрите онлайн словил вы пели но
how did Kazan enter the territory of this
как казань вошла в территории вот этого
Moscow state
московского государства
? Initially, now Kazan began
изначально сейчас казани началась
from this, it wasn’t Moscow that
от это не москва захватила оказали
captured Moscow;
москву захватила казань изначально
- it turns out, but there is,
наоборот как-то получается зато есть
remember the capture of Kazan there by Ivan the Terrible,
помните захват казани там иваном грозным
or who can I make a mistake, this comes to
или кем могу ошибиться такая доходит до
come to cut out everyone there who had the highest
приходил до вырезал там всех кто высшей
wheel, so
колеса вот
he tried to
он пытался
get it, and now it turns out you live
получил ну и сейчас получается вы живете
conquered Russia by Russians
покоренные россии русскими
Russian Russians, see Ukraine, too, in
русский русских смотри украина тоже по
fact, Russians, there is no Ukraine  Russian
сути русские нет украины не русские
Ukrainians and Russians, then different peoples,
украинцы и русские то разные народы
originally you and earlier included apple,
изначально вас и ранее входили apple
this was not included, they also won us
этого не входили они тоже нас завоевали
their time in this province, in
свое время вот этой провинции
short, killing 6 Russians, memory, here they are not
короче убив 6 россиян память вот их не
there promptly guys from the Arctic income
там оперативно парней из арктики доходы
freedom 2xs he is their type above the Russian
свобода 2xs он их типа выше русский
Ukrainian people you are  if you were in the USSR
украинский народ вы же были в ссср
you were a Tatar, but you would be with so so and sho you are
ты татарин же бы вы со со со и шо ты
toys one people of the Kyrgyz  PS there were reboots in the USSR,
игрушки один народ киргизы были в ссср
one people, flowers, this garbage is
перезагрузки один народ цветки это фигня
shorter in their head, that is,
короче в голове у них так то есть потому
because it is their historical horizon in this
что он их горизонт исторической в этом
review, so who is watching us from
обозрение так вот кто нас смотрит из
Russia and from the conquered peoples, you are
россии так и с покоренных народов вам
specially shown to teach history and
специально показывают вы историю учить и
in Russia, the history of Russia  there is so formidable
в россии историю россии там так грозный
there some kind of feodora is shorter than all these Ivan
там какой-то феодоры короче все эти иван
and does not tell the new history of your
и новом не рассказывает историю вашего
people the history of the Buryats the history of the
народа историю бурятов историю то-то
history of the Bashkirs somehow you
историю башкир вы как-то вы че то там
were somehow underdeveloped then
были какие-то недоразвиты потом
handed out everything you now won in the Russian
раздавали всей вы теперь в российской
Federation  the Russian and
федерации завоевали ранее российская и
Russian empire yes there
российская империя да там
if socially then that is, it turns out
если социально потом то есть получается
look we are not Russian Chechens are not Russian
смотри мы не русский чеченцы не русский
you are not Russian Tatars so Russians
вы татары не русские так русские
once captured Ukraine we are
когда-то захватили украину мы такие
Russians in fact this interesting
русские по сути вот этот интересный
question is who they are some peoples
вопрос это кто они какие-то народы
who lived there on  territory of smears
которые жили там на территории мазков
than this one, they are now called
чем этой вот они теперь называется
Russians, but the point is not the fact that
русскими но суть не в том суть том что
look, we have freed ourselves from we are developing
смотри мы освободились от мы развиваем
our language in our school  in our language,
свой язык у нас школы на нашем языке
science in our language, films in our
наука на нашем языке фильмы на нашем
language, and you were a team of masses, and in your
языке а вы команда была масс а у вас в
Tatarstan they teach you the history of Russia, they are of
татарстане учат вас историю россии они
Tatarstan, the history of the rewritten
татарстана история переписанные никогда
never taught you the [ __ ] you need to
не учил нахуй надо как акад вам
tell you what you [ __ ] up from,
рассказывать из чего вы заебали ну
that is, you are taught the fake history of Russia
то есть вам учат фейковую историю россии
and bring if the stories are rewritten, the
и привести если истории переписана
original teach that you were nobody there, and
изначальный учат шо вы там были никто а
Moscow is shorter there, just shorter, the earth is
москва она короче там прям короче земля
flat, giants exist,
плоская великаны существует были
and who are you by
существовали а вы кто по профессии
profession, yes, no one, well, you work by someone
профессии да никто ну работаете кем
but not by how, but by what you earn a
но не тем как а чем зарабатываете на
living, I
жизнь
study, otherwise you are students  that you are
учусь а то вы студенты что на кого
studying
учитесь
for the elevator of the century, it’s not you at the university
на лифте века это вы не в университете
somewhere in the school in well, in St. Petersburg now, St. Petersburg or in Kazan, now
где-то в училище на ну в питере сейчас
Kazan, so far,
питере или в казани сейчас казани пока
I’m in Kazan, they don’t teach oricon elevator,
что нахожусь в казани на лифт oricon не
but no, why is there a large higher current
учат а нету а почему большая высшая тока
i think of peter in  Kazan, look at the
i think of peter в казани смотрите в
university in Kazan, I know it’s very strong,
казани университет я знаю очень сильные
so
так
why, why can’t they teach you there
почему почему у вас вот не могут там
on the elevator of the century, so you
учить на лифта века вот по вашему
don’t have such a moment, but it’s good, but at school you
нет таких момент а хорошо а в школе вы
studied in the Tatar language or in
учились на татарском языке или на
Russian and
русском и
Ukrainian
украинском
it’s funny I’m even funny
смешно я даже смешно
on which life will be brought in at school we
на котором жизни внесут в школе мы
studied bolts of the floor boards Russian as
учились болта доски пола русский как
semi-Tatar
полу татарский
mathematics what language did you
математика на каком языке вам
teach mathematics in fact it’s not the
преподавалась математика она по сути не
same as what language we won’t
же каком языке не
teach
преподам
mountain by the way multiplication tables I know this  but
гора кстати таблиц умножение знаю это же
I also find I don’t understand who
находит я тоже не понимаю кто короче
came up with it shorter or why you are sitting in this
придумал или зачем вы сидите этой
table, but if you can add,
таблице мы же если можно прибавлять
for example, instead of 2, multiply by 100,
например вместо 2 умножить на 100
you can add 2 a hundred times, you can
можно сто раз прибавить 2 можно два раза
add twice that’s all and not suffer why
прибавить что и все и не мучиться зачем
it needs 100 rubles shortness of breath to do,
это нужно 100 рублей одышка совершать
for example  you buy for 50 rubles a type of
например ты покупаешь за 50 рублей тип
employee you really teach multiplication saucer
сотрудника вам реально блюдце умножение
if and if you buy there,
учит а если а если покупаешь там
for example, there are 10 of some robots or
например там 10 каких-то к роботам или
all the boxes were 8000 dates for .  young to
всем коробами было 8000 дату на . молода
find out the role in this
узнать роль в этом
got lost
заблудился
no wonder the simple
немудрено немудреного
10 boxes five boxes
10 коробок пять коробок
depending on how you buy here you went into
смотря как покупаешь вот вы вышли в
roulette you specifically chose Ukraine for
рулетку вы специально выбрали украину на
nothing advised well we have
нет посоветовали ну имеем души
special souls specially not
специальные специально не специально по
specially played the whole world
своим играли весь мир имею ввиду
for me I mean a mystery to me and such people lived
для меня загадкой а такие люди доживали
to be bent  then how do such people
до погнули то как вот такие люди
live to be 18 years old with such a level of
доживают до 18 лет с таким уровнем
flash intelligence, you could jump off and
интеллекта flash можно было спрыгнут и
put a sound on there and put your fingers in the socket and in
звyк на там сунут и пальцы в розетку и
short, check there and all the
короче там проверит и все таблетки типа
runny-type pills are turned on with a step rumble view of the yacht
насморк включены шагнем гул вид яхте
people generally live in the top of us so I
люди вообще живут в топе нами так я
can ammo  hansen cotton wool and a thousand
патроны может hansen ваты и тысячу вам
good luck to you mike kirov elevator i will take the sheep
удачи майк лифтом кирова я приму овцы
closely and in general
тесно и вообще
just like that immediately react to the
просто так сразу туда реагируйте на на
ukrainian flag on not badly understood
украинский флаг на не плохо не понял
stole .
выкрали .
Contours for 50 percent put on 50 g
контуры на 50 процентов затари на 50 г
volume and you
объем и вам все похуй надо
don’t give a [ __ ] even your girlfriend has the same position in life no she’s Ukrainian show me I
позиция нет она украинка покажите мне не
won’t even bother I want it and she
буду не лезь даже на хочу это и еще она
didn’t climb there for something
не лезла там на что-то
on 25 percent rain
на на 25 процентов rain
she is also on the elevator role but
она тоже на лифте роль но лифта века
there is no elevator of the century she is a crane operator
нет она крановщица
that's what you think these jokes that
вот как вы думаете вот эти шутки которые
you try children are not really funny I'm not
вы пробуете дети не реально смешные я не
joking
шучу
because I counted the apartment two times hot in
потому что я квартиру два раза накале по
Ukraine
украине
Yak-7 hot we will wash why
як-7 горячим насчитал мы помоем почему
two times maximum joked and  the fact that my
два раза максимум пошутил а то что мои
answers that seemed like jokes to you,
ответы которые вам показались шуткам
your problems,
ваш проблем
maybe you have some questions about
может у вас есть какие то вопросы к
ukraine intel doll ukraine,
украине кукле intel украине до интерес
some kind of interest arose in me now why is it
какой-то возник у меня сейчас почему
here for what for what in general in fact and
здесь за что для чего вообще по сути и
why the moment is important because of what goes on
почему важен момент из-за чего идет
at all  the key moment is going
вообще ключевой момент идет
well, so let's say
ну так скажем
these actions are going such a gay Eurovision in general
эти действия идут такие гейского вообще
that what kind of actions are the
евровидение что какие действий
actions
действия
on
на
what is this
что за это есть
[laughs]
[смех]
limited
ограниченный
you just understand, but the moment may
вы просто понимаете же не зато может
arrive
прилететь
, you have to call it  to specifically make
момент надо называть специально делать
such a face of kirenko a special
такое лицо кирпиченко специальной
military operation, here are the operations,
военная операция вот операции
why do you more or less how to survive and it
зачем вы же более менее как бы дожить и
turns out very interesting and I
получается это очень интересно и я
love it when people from Russia
обожаю когда меня люди из россии
ask me why for what and why these
спрашивают зачем для чего и почему эти
actions that cannot be called a war
действия которые нельзя назвать войной
can be so many special operations and I always
можно столько спецопераций и я всегда
they ask, imagine that I came to hit
спрашивают представьте что я пришел бью
you in the face
вам морду
with my feet, so you lie cooler and
бью раз ногами так вы круче лежите и
then
потом и
your girlfriend comes up and they don’t
ваша девушка подходит и не меня
ask me, but [ __ ] him
спрашивают а хрен его бьешь
you think why why
ты думаешь а зачем почему для чего все
all these actions are
вот эти действия
initially wrong thinking, that is,
изначально неправильное мышление то есть
maybe you need to ask someone who  it beats
может надо задавать тому кто бьет
some kind of [ __ ] this thing sense
какого-то хрена это дело смысле
wrong well tell me the right
неправильный а ну скажите правильное
thinking even if you suppose it looks like a
мышление даже если вы допустим похоже на
psychologist like you thinking and tell me the
психолог как вас мышления и скажите
correct thinking right thinking
правильности правильное мышление
when
когда
I look now on the street yes
я смотрю сейчас на улице да
it’s my sunset the
это у меня закат
birds sing all is well the
птички поют все хорошо
world above the earth the
мир над землей
genocide
геноцид
you finished  generates a random set of
вы закончили генерирует случайные набор
words
слов
he just didn't understand it didn't really
он просто не вник не реально повторить
repeat again  hey, we have my thinking, it
еще раз не понимает мы у меня мышление
’s not like him,
не такое него меня
well, put it plus who understood who has
так а ну поставьте плюс кто вник у кого
such thinking,
такое мышление
so who books what he translated into
так кто книг то что он транслировал в
this set of unrelated words, it’s
этот набор несвязанных слов это
interesting, my sister is a psychologist, let
интересно у меня сестра психолог давайте
’s she understand again and I’ll say a case of a
еще раз она она поймет и я скажу случай
set of words  what I see, yes, she will understand and
набор слов то что я вижу да она поймет и
from this it will generate some moments, but
с этого сгенерирует какие-то моменты а
you don’t, what does the word generate
вы не а что значит слово сгенерировать
generate to explain to you how interesting we are
сгенерировать вам еще объяснять как мы
words fabric generates a moment
интересны слова ткань генерирует момент
google to help not but what kind of number generates
гугл в помощь не а что за число генерит
everything means generate vinyl
все означает generate виниле
gen3 not from where  the words generate
gen3 не откуда слова генерит
generate yes, where,
генерировать да откуда
for some Anglo-Saxon, probably the
за какой-то англосаксонской наверное
word went to means soul, not here, but
слово пошло на означает душа не вот но
like
типа
heat,
тепло
maybe we shouldn’t be generated, but
может нас может надо не генерировать а
native Russian syllables generate
исконно русским слогах породить
no, generate is more suitable not
нет генерировать больше подходит не
like this, because it’s often over the hill, that is,
такие ведь это за бугор нередко то есть
without any such moments
без всяких таких моментов
to receive  one moment is correct
получать один момент правильно
from let's say there conditionally take the 5th moment
из допустим там условно возьмем 5 момент
of some of these 5 moments
каких-то из этих 5 моментов
one moment
один момент
I will explain to you in your language
я я вам вашим языком объясняю
I’ll just explain to you in your language, then
я вам вашим языком просто объясню значит
look at the river, so whether the plane can swim, but
смотрите речка так самолет ли плавать но
when it’s Saturday, you understand yes, the
когда будет суббота вы поняли да
generator is random
генератор случайных
in
в
history,
историю
but when
а вот когда
you say some snippets of phrases
вы говорите какими-то обрывками фраз
like this, you probably don’t remember the words in the ball leading to
таких так ты возможно в мяч ведущий к
the Volga River
реке
the memory is over,
не помните слова память закончилась
okay, yes, I also look like that and boring
ладно да я тоже так смотришь и скучные
meetings, or
встречи а
maybe even sing the anthem at the end,
может еще на окончание гимн спеть
no, I still want to hear the first
нет я все таки хочу услышать первый
verse of the anthem, I don’t even give manipulations
куплет гимна я аж и манипуляции не подаю
at the clock, well done, come on, I’ve been
у часов быстро молодец давай я давно
scientific for a long time, let’s have such bachata such
научный давай вот такие бачаты такие
shots gene and pout  I’m someone but you can see
кадры ген и дуешься я кого-то но видно
50500 kef said Stalin from the principle of Levin,
50500 kef сказал сталин из принцип левин
I think this is the first con of the sheep’s plan, the
я думаю на это первый кон овцы план
axis was inadequate and let’s go five
ось такие были неадекват и давай пять
in order to complete both positive
для того чтобы завершить и позитивные
notes and a
ноты и
video how awesome life was in this this
видосик как офигенно жилось в этот это
is a rubric for me to think about
вот рубрика мне короче душе подумать о
side there Zhilin this is a chance let's
бок вот там жилин это шанс давайте
delivery she like you will come here 700 than
доставка she like явится вас тут 700 чем
from 500 likes to throws and likes and we
с лайки в 500 до кидает и лайки и мы
will be
будем
2 thousand grandfather from orenburg
2 тыс деда из оренбурга
good afternoon
добрый день
hello  those I’m from Ukraine, the city of
здравствуйте я из украины город
Khmelnitskaya, what city of Russia are you from,
хмельницкая вы с какого города россии
yes, I would be lighter than a brunette high in a quarry,
да я б легче брюнетки высоко в карьер
I’m Orenburg, the southern Urals, and what in
я оренбург южный урал а что у вас в
Minsk brought you, did it already
минске занесло вас было уже ли
smell like the eighties when I, too, in the
пахнет восьмидесятом году когда я тоже в
Odessa region, our smelled famously [ __ ]
одесской области наш пахло лихо [__]
beet clean up good  military
буряк убирай хорошая военная подготовка
training you had for beetroot was removed,
у вас было на буряк убирали
but as they say, not beetroot, the attention of
но как говорят не буряка внимание
sugar factories is past, now it’s
сахарных заводов мимо я сейчас сейчас
easier now now you don’t have to drive the soldier they
проще сейчас не надо гонять солдату
chose beetroot, now there is a combine
выбирали буряк сейчас есть комбайн
that removes the beetroot, yes, it’s understandable,
который убирает бурят да понятно но
but we’re doing cuts from where
работу занимаемся порезах откуда
I just know the sea and in the union there were
я морскую просто знать и в союзе были
such  technologies that it was necessary for soldiers to
такие технологии что надо было солдат
drive beet digging manually,
гонять буряк выкапывать вручную
see now the point is the same technologies
смотрите сейчас дело в том же технологии
such that one plant
такие что один завод
can produce as much products
может произвести столько продукции
as before November 5, I understand, I
сколько раньше 5 ноября понимаю я говорю
say it was more than 40 years ago
же это было давно 40 с лишним лет назад
then such technologies to a place in the west
тогда такие технологии к месту на западе
back I I  I was just
назад я я просто историю от изучалась
looking for a story from where in Europe or in America the soldiers
искал где в европе или в америке солдат
were driven to drill and dig, so I didn’t find the
гоняли бурить и выкапывать вот не нашел
80s  years of
80-х годах
migrants we don’t
мигрантов не
see history well you know it’s bad it’s a
видим истории хорошо знаете плохо
little bad
немножко плохо
it’s working out let’s take for example Italy
получается возьмем например италию
France yes there Latinos worked in the fields
францию да там на полях работали
until the
латиносы до
black black continent work you in the
черный черный континент работу вы 80-х
80s yes yes and who doesn’t I just thought from
годах да да а кто нет я просто думал от
us to
нас на
Germany how the Turks thought how the bricks
германию как подумали турки как брики
dug
копали
maybe  either the
может быть либо реки
rivers didn’t have enough work to turn the Turks to
работу не хватало они превращению турок
denunciation and now drill, and if
доносу и вот пробурить и если была
Germany was divided into two parts of the GDR and the
германия разделена на две части гдр и
FRG and the GDR under the Soviet Union, as
фрг и гдр под советским союзом я так
I understand it, there the soldiers were digging the boo of the river and
понимаю что там солдаты копали бу реки а
in Sergio who would have dug the rivers and who
в сергио кто копал бы реки а кто вам
told you that  in the GDR, amulets dig
сказал что в гдр обереги копать
someone fell from where there sugar was
кто-то упал откуда там сахар был
then lungs, you can
то легких вы может
they didn’t do agriculture until the
они сельским хозяйством не занимались до
hips didn’t occupy agriculture
бёдер не занимал сельском хозяйстве
will be different for example time to use
будет другая например time to use
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
[music]
[музыка]
Bashkiria was engaged in a storm chamber of Ukraine
башкирии занималась буря камере украины
and
а
now now in Russia only  the Bashkirs
сейчас сейчас в россии только башкиры до
are engaged in storms no comments now, not
занимаются бури коменты нет сейчас не
only the fighters are now
только борцы сейчас
occupying the black earth
на черноземе занимают и
and the Bashkiria are occupying, do you think that it’s
и башкирии занимают вы считайте что
right that in  as a soldier in the
правильно что у вас как солдата в
Soviet Union they used it as a
советском союзе использовали как
free labor force in order to collect rivers of tons
бесплатную рабочую силу дабы реки тонн
for leaving, well, that’s who it’s logical and
собирать на уход ну вот кого логично и
love food, well, Vince, you took him in the army without a
питания люби ну вот винс вы же в армии
cost there you can and
его забирала безкоштовно там ты можешь и
rallied now we
сплотил сейчас мы
are essentially a crab because supposedly it’s normal for work
по сути краб потому что якобы за работа
it was paid to be a lot of
нормально оплачивалась то было быть куча
adoring so still life toyota head
обожающих так натюрморт тойоте голове
without cost of labor and now it’s logical
безкоштовно рабочую силу и вот логично
food you can already predict the springs of a free country
питание ты уже пружин свободной стране
, etc.
можешь предсказать и т.п.
it was wrong to shoot because the soldier
неправильно было shot ибо солдатиком
drove and the bricks of the cop the
гонял и брики копат
worker at the factory receives money for
рабочий на заводе получает деньги за
his work, so the avaza of the soldier was taken to
свою работу так аваза солдата взяли
serve the young one and threw it for free
служит молодого и бесплатно кинули
to collect storms in the movie field for some reason why the
собирать бури кино поле почему то почему
worker receives money for his work and
рабочий получает за свою работу деньги а
you, as a soldier, do it for free, and we
вы как солдат бесплатно это делаете а мы
got us  they also got how
получали мы тоже получали сколько
much someone got good money on
это кто-то хорошие деньги получал на
cars
машинах
worked well
работал хорошо
soldiers of the Soviet army
солдаты советской армии хорошо
make good money pay extra I
зарабатывать доплатить я я
also served every waffle not-not-not that
служил тоже каждую вафель не-не-не что
you served conscripts lekin yes yes yes and
вы срочникам служили lekin да да да и
how much you were paid
сколько вам платили
does not remember the grade passed again rubles by
не помнит сорт прошло опять рублей по
apartment 5 rubles for 100 per month
квартире 5 рублей за 100 за месяц
but it doesn’t
но это не имеет значения
matter for a month 5 rubles
имеет за месяц 5 рублей
for a loaf of bread something like 20 kopecks it
на буханка хлеба что-то копеек 20 вроде
cost
стоило
well let’s do it if 10 kopecks it
хорошо давайте так если 10 копеек это
turns out
получается
12 costs you 50 loaves of bread you
12 стоит у вас 50 буханок хлеба вам
were paid for a month and
месяц платили да и
I just wanted to  to understand the amount of this payment for this is
я хотел понять размер этой оплаты на это
cool cool because someone else
круто круто потому что кто то кто то и
could not work for 50 loaves at work, but
не мог на 50 буханок за работой да
just worked for free
просто бесплатно работал
if I came here  I want to understand you were taken
если сюда я хочу понять вас забирали вы
away, you lived there for two years in the barracks, ate
гособеспечении жили в казарме ели там
butter, bread, and you also had vaseline, and
масло хлеб еще вас вазелина бу реки и
paid about five rubles a month for
платили где-то пять рублей месяц на
briquettes, and how
брикеты там больше зарабатывал а сколько
much I’m interested in, because this story hides from us, what difference does it make to
сколько мне интересно потому что от нас
you  what it is I want to understand to my liking,
для чего это нужно я хочу понять по душе
I found her sensor only 10 years old, I'm 81,
я застал ее сенсор только 10 лет я 81
because look, now she will tell us
потому что смотрите нам сейчас расскажет
that it was bad during the USSR, but I don’t believe, I
что при ссср было плохо а я не верю я
want to figure out
хочу разобраться
how it is with you,
как у тебя
because now I’m
потому что у меня сейчас то на украину я
born in Ukraine in the USSR
родился в ссср
let's not top up what you don't believe,
ты давай не доливаем что ты не верь ну
well, really, look at me senior, we
так реально вот смотрите мне старший мы
our people tell some that it was
наши люди рассказывают одни что было
bad, others that it was
плохо другие что было хорошо я хочу
good  numbers began
дошли до конкретных чисел что-то стали
to burn something to
подгорать до
burn at
подгорать на
once grandmother impudent well, yes, what can
сразу бабушка дерзкий ну да а что я могу
I tell you and the people grandmother who
тебе рассказать и народа бабушка которые
grandmother mother can grandmother already
бабушкой мать может на бабу бабушка уже
calls
вызывает
queues for bread  ohm, I remember the
очереди за хлебом были помню
line for bread on the left, they were
очередь за хлебом левом были на
maybe brighter, we keep it not directly above, it
может быть ярче держим это не прямо над
would never be busy for me for bread and
никогда не бы не занято мне за хлебом и
there was no queue to give them, and
не дать им не было очереди а вы сейчас
now you will live in Orenburg now,
вот вы сейчас в оренбурге доживете
we have, and where
мы имеет а где
in the Orenburg region
по оренбургской области
will you look  you support this war
посмотрите вы поддерживаете эту войну
against ukraine,
против украины
they are at war, well, this show can’t be called
они по войны ну вот это шоу вас назвать
brotherhood you didn’t
спицы братство же нельзя запрещено вы не
name you support you will say you
назвали вы поддерживаете вы скажете вы
support it or not you support it
поддерживаете или нет вы поддержите ли
but you are afraid choose
но вы боитесь подбираете
support support the
поддерживать подержите
Russian operation yes
российской операции да у нас
here tell us whether you support it or not
вот скажите вы поддержите или нет
Yes, support Yes, I understand, look, and now
да поддержите да понял смотрите а теперь
I want to say Russia is a rich country,
я хочу сказать россия это богатая страна
very very rich and will give it oil,
очень очень богат и даст она имеет нефть
diamonds, gas, and where does all the money from
алмазы газ а куда идут все деньги от
these oil and gas diamonds go
этих нефтегаза алмазов
as a leader to me, but if it’s none of my business,
как мне вождем но как не мое дело
look interesting,
смотрите интересно
uncle, that is, you and your business  what is
дяденька то есть ты и твое дело что тут
happening here in ukraine and it's none of my business
происходит у нас в украине а не мое дело
what you have there and why look why
что там у тебя а почему смотри почему
grandfather is like that who sits in the Czech Republic in
дедушка такой который сидит в чехии в
Slovakia near  oh, there is no oil gas and
словакии у которой нету газа нефти и
which buys from Russia they pay Russia
которая покупает у россии платят россии
money for a view better than you from
деньги за вид лучше чем вы у
him than
него чем
I didn’t see
я не видел
no I didn’t see people here from the Czechs and
не я я не видел людей вот с чехи и
Slovaks massively and everything everything yes yes
словаки массово стал и все все все да да
yes yes and
да да и
turned on to them in the car  saving and there what
включила до их в машине saving а там че
.  who is there she is so
. кто там она уж такие до
hyung to sit in no exchange of the ussr having taken a test
хен сидеть в не обмен ссср забрав д тест
vazobral fry having taken everything
вазобрал молоди забрав все
ok inci a wedge and developed a screw live in the
ok inci клин и развивалась винт живут в
shade would be a
тенек бы
naughty villar winpe soldier solves
набу ретивый villar солдата winpe решает
this sharks the whole view even before automation
этот акулы весь вид еще до автоматизации
you are here vidose treba bulo there
ты-то тут видосе треба було там вручную
Milkmaids manually milked this and with the alliance rumpled,
доярки доил этом и при союзе помятая
there were still plans, so you have so
было еще планы надо итак тебя так у той
many of that milkmaid, but further on, but I remember the
доярки столько но дальше по а я же помню
kid at school I will go with a task from
малый в школе буду идти задачей из
mathematics trackid android your there,
математики trackid android ваши там
such a milkmaid squeezed out so much milk 6c
такая доярка выдавила столько молока 6c
and you solved it there for  1 cl and technology
и ты там решал это за 1 кл и технологий
in this ti
в этом ti
auto yes trees there auto brain her
авто да ёлки там авто мозгового нее
pharma and and
фарме и и
diversa and you think like people want to hit the
diversa и думаешь як люды хочет вот в
target [ __ ] term vert so you wish
цель долбанный срок верта так ты желаешь
you bachish us kicks
ты бачишь нас кики
further cooler and still a lot of 0 from
дальнейшее круче и все же много 0 из
houses to the thread
домов до ниточки
of the payments department
отдела выплат
or  delivering Peter the good to honor the
или доставку петр добрых на почтить
feat of the place you pout our stream of them sho
подвиг о места дуешься наш стрим них шо
who wants a repair channel in the office in the chat
кто хочет ремонтный канал в офисе в чат
and send messages, you can need to over this and
и куе посылания можно надо над этим и
teach how it keeps
научить обовязково как он держит от
lingual extrusion from easily places  elk yes you
легко местах язычной выдавилось да вы
were and I will be surprised what kind of
находилась а я буду удивляться я какие
light bulbs you can get on the winter road and
лампочки на зимнику ли и добудешь и
flowers to ukraine in europe here you can go to
цветы украине в европе здесь можно в
australia 2 i.e. antarctica us david
австралию 2 то есть антарктиды нас дэвид
distance vernadian show here is this vidos
дистанции вернадский шоу вотъ этом видос
on may 3 musya their freedom of the good glory to
на 3 мая муся их свобода добрых слава
ukraine
украине
[music]
[музыка]